fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
I've... had it...
Oh, Sakura-chan!
For crying out loud,
how far have we walked?
The tower hasn't gotten a bit closer.
Here we can see it
right in front of our eyes.
Strange...
No mistake about it.
It seems that we're already within
the enthusiastic welcome.
Take a look at that.
Huh?
Oh, that can't be!
What on earth is going on?!
No way!
Is it Genjutsu...?
So it seems.
We were lured in perfectly.
It appears we were meticulously careful,
and were made to walk
around the same place in a circle.
We're being watched...
Probably.
They intend to wear down
our physical strength and
catch us unprepared when
we're bone-tired.
If so, then this follows the enemy strategy.
Then... They'll be coming soon.
Humph, they've appeared.
This is the perfect handicap.
Replication
Match!
I'm the Main Character!
W-What is this?
It's quite a number.
Moreover, they're clones?
Cornered rats.
Shut up!
Oh, they're quite weak, huh?
Good!
Naruto!
W-What are these guys?
W-What's going on here?
I'll assess this!
Sharingan!
Naruto!
Sasuke!
Sasuke-kun!
W-What's going on?
My body's...
Are you okay?
No mistake.
It's the real thing, not an illusion.
— Scroll please.
That Kabuto-san was injured means
these things are actual Shadow Clones?!
B-But... even though Shadow clones
are supposed to vanish
if they take a direct attack,
these things don't vanish.
Does it mean then this is Genjutsu?!
Which is it?!
Scroll please.
Give me scroll.
Damn it!
It's futile!
Stop!
These things are illusions.
It's an enemy Genjutsu.
B-But, Kabuto-san's wound is the real thing.
No, it's as Sasuke-kun says.
Probably the enemy is hiding somewhere...
and coordinating their attack with
movements of the "Genjutsu Shinobi"
and attacking from a different location.
Pretending as if those
Genjutsu Shinobi are attacking.
— Scroll please.
Then I'll find the idiot who's behind
the scenes
throwing Kunai knives
and kick his butt!
Hold it, Naruto-kun.
We've been deceived as
to the source of the Kunai knives...
so we can't discover the precise
location of the enemy like this.
Do you get it?
That is the enemy's purpose.
From a data standpoint, it's a type
who is weak at close combat
and Taijutsu that likes
this kind of attack.
The true enemy won't come out until we can't move at all.
Listen, everyone!
In any case,
all there is to do now is to fend
off the enemy attack.
Fine, if that's what their plan is...
Now then...
I wonder how far they can hold out.
The night is long.
Man!
This is endless!
Since it's come to this...!
Stop!
Naruto-kun, don't waste your Chakra!
Even if you attack these things,
there's no point!
If I hit them all in
a single sweep,
the enemy won't fire inadvertently
while these things are reverting back.
The hiding place will
be discovered, so.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Shadow Clones?!
It's not over yet!
Sasuke-kun, what should we do...?
Man, that useless...
All there is to do is go for it!
B-But...
Indeed...
It's not a situation that
he can get through by himself.
Let's go, Sakura!
Y-Yeah!
I'm not finished yet...
Dawn is breaking.
It's finally time for the hunt.
Mubi, that's enough.
We're finished hunting their spirits.
Now what's left is just their bodies.
Lucky.
You're... the one who...
did my left shoulder.
I finally found you.
You really hung me up.
Lucky.
I can finally even the score.
You... really hung me up.
Lucky.
I can finally even the score.
Heh!
Cornered rats.
It went well, Naruto!
W-What the hell
are these guys?!
T-This can't be!
Since when...?!
Idiot!
You finally showed your
true colors, punk!
T-This brat, don't tell me...
The Shadow Clone is just
the preparation for the trick...
for me to portray every member
of the team by myself!
At the same time Naruto
lifted the Shadow Clone,
the three of us hid.
The Genjutsu users were
adversely deceived.
Naruto!
Naruto, you've used too much Chakra.
I'll do the rest.
No way! I'm not always going to have
the good parts taken away!
Is this really that Naruto...?
Since when had he improved
this much?
That's some brat...
I can't believe he can still move.
Naruto...
Amazing Chakra stamina...
Right after
a Multiple Shadow Clone Jutsu...
a daring technique that transforms just
three of the bodies into his companions.
To think he can still move
even after doing all that.
Here it's the fifth day now.
This kid will transform
if he can just master
the use of his Chakra.
Not bad.
But we're still not unlucky.
There's no time.
This time around,
we'll show you our Ninjutsu!
Ninja Art: Fog Clone Jutsu!
Shadow clones?
No, they are plain clones.
However, he's up to something.
Be careful!
Hah! If they are just clones,
then there's one real body.
I'll kick their butts right
and left until I run into him.
You idiot.
Such a tactless thing...
I'm telling you!
I'm saying don't stick your nose in!
Naruto!
That's reckless!
Jeez!
From earlier, the nape of my neck
hurts when I use the Sharingan.
Maybe I used too much Chakra.
Damn it!
Damn it. A clone?!
This one, too?!
Naruto-kun! Stop!
Are they all fakes?!
Or could it be Genjutsu again?!
This is... the last... Chakra.
Sharingan!
Sasuke-kun!
The bruise again...
Stop using the Sharingan, Sasuke-kun!
It won't do to create an opening!
Kabuto-san!
Damn it!
Stop! Naruto!
No matter how much
you swing at them,
the real body isn't in those clones.
Then where's the enemy
attacking us from?!
If they are merely clones,
the clones themselves can't attack!
If I knew that, we wouldn't be
having a rough time of it!
This is the enemy's scheme.
Man, I can't use
the Shadow Clone Jutsu anymore...
They've about reached their limit.
Lucky.
That's it!
The real body hides with
the Earth Style Jutsu
and attacks from behind a clone!
Kabuto-san!
Heh, "it won't do to
create an opening," right?!
Thank you, Naruto-kun.
You saved me.
We're okay here, Naruto!
What happened there? Are you hurt?
That's a terrible bruise.
It's nothing.
Here it is, here it is!
Look, the Heaven scroll!
Good for you.
There's something about this guy...
that I don't like.
Oh, it's you guys.
You're late, Kabuto.
I got a bit involved in something.
Sorry.
But, but...
thanks to you, we got both the scrolls.
No, it's because you guys fought hard.
You were amazing
at the end, Naruto-kun.
We're going through this door.
Well then, I wish us both luck.
Yeah!
What of the harvest?
Yes.
More than I expected.
I filled in his entire data
from this second exam.
You need this, right?
So, how was it?
Sure enough, it appears you're curious.
Orochimaru-sama.
I want to ask your opinion.
As a Sound Village's spy...
That's not necessary, is it?
You will be the one to decide it all, so...
I like that cleverness of yours.
Good work.
There's nobody here.
I'm okay now, Sakura.
O-Okay.
That's too bad!
Shannaro!
Hey, hey, what're we supposed to do?
Oh! Look at that...
Without... Heaven...
I don't get it at all.
If "Heaven" does not exist,
enrich your knowledge,
and prepare for the chance.
If "Earth" does not exist,
run the fields in search
of an advantage.
Open the series of
Heaven and Earth,
and the perilous way
shall be redressed...
This is namely the secret of
"the one that guides..."
What's that?
It looks like there are letters
or something missing there.
It's probably has to do with the scroll.
I think this means we're supposed
to open the Heaven & Earth scroll.
Okay then, I'm going to open it.
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
What's this, what's this?
Here I thought that the really
strong ones were remaining,
but Hinata, Kiba, Shikamaru,
all of the Leaf Village rookies are here.
And that Lee's team, too.
So much for getting all inflated.
Well, I'm the man who's going
to become the Hokage.
I must impress them and
show that I'm not in the same class
as any ordinary blockhead!
Next episode:
"The Second Exam Completed! All of Them Are Here, The Rookie Nine!"